JACE REINKE

+1 (417) 693-3615 \$\rightarrow\$ Springfield, MO

reinkejace@gmail.com ♦ linkedin.com/in/jreinke428 ♦ jreinke428.github.io

A college senior with nearly three years of professional experience pursuing a career in software engineering. He is a quick learner with a keen interest in problem-solving and thrives in team environments. Experienced in various programming languages and technologies and strong in essential computer science concepts. Seeking a position as a full-stack developer yet open to exploring any role that allows him to contribute his skills and learn from seasoned professionals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O'Reilly Auto Parts - Junior Software Developer August 2022 - present

- Works in a full-stack environment under the Supply Chain vertical to improve and maintain various web apps relating to auto parts ordering and logistics.
- Pioneered the adoption of Vue.js and TypeScript within his team, establishing new development standards in UI/UX design through the creation of a new component library used in 5 applications thus far.
- Practices Agile methodologies to enhance team collaboration and efficiency, while integrating DevOps practices to streamline the CI/CD pipeline, ensuring rapid, reliable deployment and maintenance of numerous applications.

O'Reilly Auto Parts - Software Developer Intern May 2022 - August 2022

- Worked in a 12 week boot-camp-like environment in full stack web development.
- Implemented various projects using Java, Spring, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and MySQL.
- Completed internship with a 97% average on all assessments.

PaperWise - Intern May 2021 - Aug 2021

- Expertly assisted customers with technical issues related to our software, leveraging product knowledge and problem-solving skills to ensure swift resolutions.
- Practiced database management using Microsoft SQL Server, focusing on optimizing data storage, ensuring data integrity, and efficient data retrieval.

SELECT PROJECTS

Snipbit Vue, TypeScript, PrimeVue, Tailwind CSS, Pocketbase

- Teamed up with a colleague to develop a social media web application for developers to store and share code snippets, integrating a sophisticated code playground with an editor utilizing IntelliSense and a live preview for HTML/CSS/JS code.
- Won 3rd place overall at Mizzou's 2023 TigerHacks hackathon out of 59 projects and 185 participants, published on Devpost.

Tabs TypeScript, JavaScript, React Native, Firebase

- Collaborated with a peer to develop a mobile application utilizing geolocation tracking, aimed at preventing drunk driving by facilitating group coordination and monitoring.
- Won 3rd place overall at Mizzou's 2022 TigerHacks hackathon out of 80 projects and 300 participants, published on Devpost.

Echoes Of Existence Godot, GDScript

- Worked with a partner to create a 2D top-down game in the Godot game engine, featuring all original art, sounds, music, as well as procedural world generation and integrated flowfield pathfinding.
- Won 3rd place overall at Adroit Studios's Game Jam and is published on itch.io.

SKILLS

Languages TypeScript/JavaScript, Java, SQL, Dart, C, Python, Swift, Groovy

Technologies Vue.js, Spring, Tailwind CSS, React, Flutter, Node, MySQL, Git, Jira, Jenkins

Soft Skills Teamwork, Communication, Problem Solving, Design, Accountability, Organization, Consistency

EDUCATION

BS in Computer Science – Drury University
BA in Mathematics – Drury University

August 2020 - May 2024

ACT: 35 - GPA: 3.63

Coursework Application Development 1/2, Research and Development 1/2, Software Engineering, Data Structures, Algorithms